Urban legends are often the unwritten beliefs that people have and announce to others.
Well, what are the unwritten rules for women about dating.
This is Dr. Paul, author of Boomer Girls, a boomer woman's guide to men and dating and host of Ask Dr. Paul.
If they're unwritten, then how do we know them?
Well, they're passed on, and the best thing I can say about unwritten rules is do not depend on another woman, as a woman, to give you valid information.
Guess what, ladies, they're as equally involved with finding the answers as you are, and they're not going to find them from asking you because you're also asking them.
It's a vicious cycle.
If you have questions, as I often say, if you want to find out about a man, why ask a woman, ask a man, ask Dr. Paul.
If you're at the point, where you're asking your girlfriends for their opinions and their input, then you're doing the wrong thing.
So, the unwritten beliefs that you're going to get, that data that you need, from your girl friends, is totally, absolutely, unequivocally wrong.
They're no more successful than you are. The probability is you're more successful They may have their own agenda as well.
So, I would say the first unwritten rule is do not depend on your girl friends to give you valid input for your choices.
That's what it's all about.
This is Dr. Paul.
May your fantasies of today be your realities of tomorrow.